<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stories</string>
    <string name="share_with_friends">Share with friends</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>


    <string name="email_feedback">blueroomxyz@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="asd">In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a \n\n\ntown of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town \n\n\n\nof Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. \n\nHe was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at In a town of Shimla, there was a very passionate and high dreamer teen, Prakhar Negi. He was very fine at </string>
    <string name="no_story_yet">No Story Yet!</string>
    <string name="more_stories_are_coming_soon">More Stories are coming soon..</string>


</resources>